<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Unlock Myanmar</title>
    <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar" />
    <updated>2019-05-22T18:16:36+06:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Mandalay–Bagan-Inle Lake-Yangon</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/inle-lake.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/inle-lake.html</id>

        <updated>2020-02-13T10:16:00+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/DSCF4549ek.jpg" alt="" />
                    Classic Myanmar Tour (7 Days/8 Nights) The classic tour of Myanmar takes&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/DSCF4549ek.jpg" alt="" />
                <div class="trip-short-desc">
<p>Classic Myanmar Tour (7 Days/8 Nights) The classic tour of Myanmar takes in the unmissable highlights of the country, including the ancient temples of Bagan, the serenity of Inle Lake, the historical city of Mandalay, the last kingdom of Myanmar, and Yangon, home to the spectacular Shwedagon Pagoda.</p>
</div>
<div class="wp-travel-trip-meta-info">
<ul>
<li>
<div class="travel-info"><strong class="title">Trip Type</strong></div>
<div class="travel-info"><span class="value"> <a href="https://www.unlockmyanmar.com/trip-type/sightseeing/" rel="tag">Sightseeing</a> </span></div>
</li>
<li>
<div class="travel-info"><strong class="title">Activities</strong></div>
<div class="travel-info"><span class="value"> No Activities </span></div>
</li>
<li>
<div class="travel-info"><strong class="title">Group Size</strong></div>
<div class="travel-info"><span class="value"> No Size Limit </span></div>
</li>
<li>
<div class="travel-info"><strong class="title">Reviews</strong></div>
<div class="travel-info"><span class="value"> <a href="javascript:void(0)" class="wp-travel-count-info">0 reviews</a> </span></div>
</li>
<li>
<div class="travel-info"><strong class="title">Trip Duration</strong></div>
<div class="travel-info"><span class="value"> 7 Day(s) 8 Night(s) </span></div>
</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<div id="overview" class="tab-list-content">
<p><strong>Classic Myanmar Tour (7 Days/8 Nights)</strong></p>
<p>The classic tour of Myanmar takes in the unmissable highlights of the country, including the ancient temples of Bagan, the serenity of Inle Lake, the historical city of Mandalay, the last kingdom of Myanmar, and Yangon, home to the spectacular Shwedagon Pagoda.</p>
<div class="wp-travel-trip-details"> </div>
</div>
<div id="trip_outline" class="tab-list-content">
<p><strong>Mandalay–Bagan-Inle Lake-Yangon</strong></p>
<p><em>The exact trip will be tailored to your wishes, dependent on on your time available and budget.</em></p>
<p>Day 1</p>
<p>Visit the three Ancient Cities of Sagaing, Amarapura and Ava (Innwa) surrounding Mandalay, exploring its history, ending the day with sunset at the famous U Bein bridge (the oldest teak bridge in the world).</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Day 2</p>
<p>Take the boat along the Irrawaddy to the magnificent ruin of Mingun, the towering 18th century temple overlooking the river, the nearby 90-ton bell from that era and the stunning and brilliantly white Myatheindan Pagoda.<br> Back to Mandalay, the tour will take you to the “Kuthodaw Pagoda”, fondly known as the world’s largest book, as well as the Golden Palace Monastery. The day will end at Mandalay Hill for sunset and the stunning view over the city.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Day 3</p>
<p>It’s an early start to catch the boat down the Irrawaddy River to Bagan. You will be able to take in the sights and sound of river life, arriving in the late afternoon just as the sun is setting over the Bagan temples</p>
<p> </p>
</div>
<div id="trip_includes" class="tab-list-content">
<p>As with all our trips they can be tailored to suit your needs and itinery, but would normally include all transfers, transportation, accommodation, entrance and guide fees</p>
<div class="wp-travel-trip-details"> </div>
</div>
<div id="trip_excludes" class="tab-list-content">
<p>As with all our trips they can be tailored to suit your needs and itinery, but would normally not include meals.</p>
<p>Insurance not included</p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/gallery/DSCF0685ek.jpg" ><img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/gallery/DSCF0685ek-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/gallery/DSCF0699ek.jpg" ><img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/gallery/DSCF0699ek-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/gallery/DSCF754.jpg" ><img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/gallery/DSCF754-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/gallery/DSCF2592ek.jpg" ><img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/4/gallery/DSCF2592ek-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ngapali Beach</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/ngapali-beach.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/ngapali-beach.html</id>

        <updated>2019-03-28T17:06:49+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    The best white sand beach in Myanmar, Ngapali Beach is situated in&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                The best white sand beach in Myanmar, Ngapali Beach is situated in Rakhine state and famous<br>for its palm trees and clear waters of the Bay of Bengal. Ngapali Beach is one of the loveliest places in Myanmar; it is also one of the most un-spoilt beaches in the world. Not so far from the hotels, there are the fisherman villages. Seeing them fishing is just authentic. As many of us now live in crowded cities with the stress and strain of over-population, we need periods of relaxation away from urban areas, and go back closer to nature. Ngapali is accessible by flight which takes about 1 hour from Yangon, by car about 14 hours drive along the Rakhine Yoma mountain range.
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mawlamyine</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/mawlamyine.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/mawlamyine.html</id>

        <updated>2019-04-09T11:24:47+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It was the first capital of British Burma, the setting of George&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                It was the first capital of British Burma, the setting of George Orwell’s famous 1936 memoir <strong>Shooting an Elephant</strong>. Still today, it is the important seaport and trading center in the south-eastern part of Myanmar. The first Baptist church in Myanmar and other colonial buildings, Bilu Island, world biggest reclining Buddha on the Kyauktalon Mountain, Kawgoon and Payon Caves are the main attractions. For those who want to try a bit of meditation at a peaceful place, or experience what it is like to be a monk, visit  the famous Pa-Auk forest monastery. Learn how to meditate from a professional mentor and experience tranquility.
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hsipaw</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/hsipaw.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/hsipaw.html</id>

        <updated>2019-04-09T11:24:24+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hsipaw is situated northern part of Shan state. We could call it&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                Hsipaw is situated northern part of Shan state. We could call it as a Shan royal city in the past. It is historically rich and the book called “Twilight over Burma” is a great book describing the tragic events. The town is also famous with its nature too. Some tourists even prefer the trekking here than in Kalaw or anywhere in northern Thailand. Having the train ride to Hsipaw is also something special, you will pass by the famous Goke Hteik Viaduct.
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Kalaw</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/kalaw.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/kalaw.html</id>

        <updated>2019-04-09T11:24:03+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/11/Kalaw.jpg" alt="" />
                    One of the few great trek destinations in Myanmar, Kalaw is an&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/11/Kalaw.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>One of the few great trek destinations in Myanmar, Kalaw is an easy place to get the trekking experience and kick back for a few days to relax. The weather is pleasant and cold and the town is also notable for its significant population of Nepali Gurkhas and Indians, whose ancestors came here to build the roads and railway during the colonial era. You can reach to Inle – Naung Shwe by train or car or trekking enjoying the scenery of Kalaw.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Kawthaung</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/kawthaung.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/kawthaung.html</id>

        <updated>2019-04-09T11:23:47+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/10/Kawthaung.jpg" alt="" />
                    When you hear the name of this country, Myanmar, you might be&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/10/Kawthaung.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>When you hear the name of this country, Myanmar, you might be picturing temples and monasteries but, in fact, it’s much more than that. The country is rich with the gifts from the mother nature. Kawthaung, called Victoria point to the British, is southernmost part of the country and over 800 gorgeous islands are near there. The city is packed with attractions and adventure. Go there before a lot of people notice it. That is the place you should visit among the beautiful Myanmar destinations  if you love adventure, water activities like snorkeling, diving, and visiting to the local fishermen houses at remote islands. Well, if you are honeymooners, surely nowhere can make you feel special than this place.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Golden Rock</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/golden-rock.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/golden-rock.html</id>

        <updated>2019-04-09T11:23:28+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/8/P7080010.jpg" alt="" />
                    Kyaikhtiyoe Pagoda, also known as Golden Rock, is one of the main&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/8/P7080010.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Kyaikhtiyoe Pagoda, also known as Golden Rock, is one of the main pilgrimage sites for local people, you don’t want to miss that place as it is one of the top ten destinations in Myanmar. Only 4 hours drive from Yangon, the pagoda is situated on the mountain cliff, only 18 ft. height. It is strongly believed as a wishful stupa. If you love short trekking, do that from Kimpun Base Camp or you can now have the cable car ride from Yathae Taung to the top of the mountain, where the stupa is. You can do the day trip from Yangon but we totally recommend to stay overnight there for it’s breathtaking sunset and sunrise views. If you are here in March, that’s the perfect time for it’s Pagoda festival.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Chin State</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/chin-state.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/chin-state.html</id>

        <updated>2019-04-09T11:23:07+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/7/Chin.jpg" alt="" />
                    Located on the ridge of 4700ft high in the southern Chin State.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/7/Chin.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Located on the ridge of 4700ft high in the southern Chin State. The town is habited by five different of Chin tribes out of fifty and over. Although most of them believe in Christianity and Buddhism, Animism is also still being practiced, a lot of stone tombs and sacrificial poles can still be seen. The town is famous for its beautiful trekking trails to villages, greeny hill-side plantations and mithun farming. Visiting to face tattooed ladies houses and having the chat with them in person is the best part. Organic fruits are super delicious here. Traditional clothing and smoked mythan meat are the best presents to home from this beautiful city.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Putao</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/putao.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/putao.html</id>

        <updated>2019-04-09T11:22:48+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/6/Putao.jpg" alt="" />
                    Situated in Kachin State, far north of Myanmar. The town is surrounded&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/6/Putao.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Situated in Kachin State, far north of Myanmar. The town is surrounded by snow-capped mountains, beautiful and clean rivers and deep forests. If you are adventurous, no doubt, Putao is the right spot for you. The only place you can visit to the snow-capped mountains in the whole south-east Asia countries. You can do hiking through in Himalayan ridges, white water rafting, kayaking, bird watching and so much more. Getting round beautiful Putao, trekking along Mula Creek, and having the breathtaking views of snow-capped mountains  will definitely make your visit worth.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bagan</title>
        <author>
            <name>Unlock Myanmar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/bagan.html"/>
        <id>https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/bagan.html</id>

        <updated>2019-03-25T14:20:19+06:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/3/DSCF2588ek.jpg" alt="" />
                    Over 2230 temples and its empire ruins make Bagan magical. People often&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://crcx-prod.github.io/unlock-myanmar/media/posts/3/DSCF2588ek.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Over 2230 temples and its empire ruins make Bagan magical. People often say, “Pictures don’t do justice ”when they witness the view of this old capital in person.</p>
<p>It was a powerful kingdom from the 11th  to 13th  century, Kings and their people built thousands and thousands of Buddhist monuments showing how the kingdom was powerful. This is the place where it all started; the culture, arts, religion of the people of Myanmar today.</p>
<p>For so sure, it is the most popular tourist destination in the country. Some tourist noticed Bagan even before they hear the name of the country, Myanmar. Bagan has been hit by earthquakes over the centuries. The most recent, in August 2016, damaged 400 temples; work on repairing them is ongoing.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
